{
    "subject": "Henry_IV_of_France",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Margaret_of_Valois",
    "human_readable": "Henry IV of France is married to Margaret of Valois.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9882772564888,
            "question": "Was there a marriage between Henry IV of France and Margaret of Valois?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.947998583316803,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Henry IV of France and Margaret of Valois?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.912413477897644,
            "question": "To whom was Henry IV of France married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9066615700721741,
            "question": "Who is Henry IV of France married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9004583358764648,
            "question": "Was Henry IV of France married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.886986494064331,
            "question": "Who was Margaret of Valois married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8150694966316223,
            "question": "Identify the wife of Henry IV of France."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7649244070053101,
            "question": "What is the name of Henry IV of France's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7357282638549805,
            "question": "What is the name of Henry IV of France's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7102653384208679,
            "question": "Who was Margaret of Valois?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Henry IV of France is married to Margaret of Valois.",
            "html": "yago_28035_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Henry IV of France's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_28035_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Henry IV of France's wife?",
            "html": "yago_28035_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Identify the wife of Henry IV of France.",
            "html": "yago_28035_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28035_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28035_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28035_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28035_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28035_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28035_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28035_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28035_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28035_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28035_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references confirming that Henry IV of France was married to Margaret of Valois. For example, from `29.txt` and `37.txt`, it is explicitly mentioned that Margaret of Valois was the first wife of King Henry IV of France."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}